

tylersanguinette.com hello@tylersanguinette.com +1 (314) 724-8413

PROFILE

An adaptable and responsible professional seeking a role in print and web design that utilizes skills developed through a diverse range of internship-based knowledge and employment. Completed 1 year in a startup company designing client based projects. Designed, developed, and launched a project, Type Quest, that recieved industry-wide recognition including Adobe Typekit.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI - ST. LOUIS

Bachelor of Fine Arts, Spring 2015 Major: Graphic Design / Minor: Art History

UNIVERSITY OF EAST ANGLIA

Norwich, England (Semester Abroad) Autumn 2014 Contemporary Gallery and Museum Studies (Art History)

EXPERIENCE

GRAIN. INC.

ASSOCIATE DESIGNER

January 2015 - Current | grainforall.com

Meets client and company needs through design strategy and creative execution. Tasks include generating and executing concepts for vector illustrations, creating UX wireframes and UI designs for responsive websites along with iOS apps, translating website designs into HTML5/CSS3, and producing magazine and booklet print spreads.

PARADOWSKI CREATIVE

INTERACTIVE/PRINT DESIGN INTERN
July 2014 - August 2014 | paradowski.com

Redesigned Operation Food Search's company brochure, concepted/ designed static and interactive banner ads, and created marketing emails.

UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI-ST. LOUIS

STUDENT ASSISTANT PROFESSIONAL January 2011 - May 2014 | umsl.jobs

Maintained information and graphics for the UMSL Human Resources website including the UMSL.jobs brand across various social media platforms and website. Produced print and web designs for other campus and UM system departments.

TYPEFOUNDING

DESIGN INTERN

June 2013 - August 2013 | typefounding.com

Proofed webfonts, coded webfont type specimens, designed and coded a single splash page, started a sans-serif typeface, and catalogued books.

SKILLS

Able to prioritise, manage time well, meet deadlines, have empathy, collaborate, problem solve, organise, and be attentive to detail.

Proficient in Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, RoboFont, HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, wireframing, Pages, Keynote, and Numbers.

Basic knowledge in Command Line, Git, JavaScript, PHP, Markdown, Sketch.

References available upon request.